<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HABits Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>HABits Lab</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu4d308fce03ad9277f815ecc9f502b7a0_31004_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>HABits Lab</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Policy summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Device permissions for Personal Data access
Device permissions for Personal Data access
Personal Data: Camera permission&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location-based interactions
Geolocation
Personal Data: geographic position&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full policy
Owner and Data Controller
Types of Data collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: geographic position; Camera permission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Application.
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Application is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. In cases where this Application specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Application or by the owners of third-party services used by this Application serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party&amp;rsquo;s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mode and place of processing the Data
Methods of processing
The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Application (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Legal basis of processing
The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.
In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Place
The Data is processed at the Owner&amp;rsquo;s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the User&amp;rsquo;s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User&amp;rsquo;s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retention time
Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.
The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purposes of processing
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Service, comply with its legal obligations, respond to enforcement requests, protect its rights and interests (or those of its Users or third parties), detect any malicious or fraudulent activity, as well as the following: Location-based interactions and Device permissions for Personal Data access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For specific information about the Personal Data used for each purpose, the User may refer to the section “Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Device permissions for Personal Data access
Depending on the User&amp;rsquo;s specific device, this Application may request certain permissions that allow it to access the User&amp;rsquo;s device Data as described below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By default, these permissions must be granted by the User before the respective information can be accessed. Once the permission has been given, it can be revoked by the User at any time. In order to revoke these permissions, Users may refer to the device settings or contact the Owner for support at the contact details provided in the present document.
The exact procedure for controlling app permissions may be dependent on the User&amp;rsquo;s device and software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that the revoking of such permissions might impact the proper functioning of this Application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If User grants any of the permissions listed below, the respective Personal Data may be processed (i.e accessed to, modified or removed) by this Application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Camera permission
Used for accessing the camera or capturing images and video from the device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Device permissions for Personal Data access
Location-based interactions
The rights of Users
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In particular, Users have the right to do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User&amp;rsquo;s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.
Details about the right to object to processing
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to exercise these rights
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information about Data collection and processing
Legal action
The User&amp;rsquo;s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related Services.
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information about User&amp;rsquo;s Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System logs and maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information not contained in this policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How “Do Not Track” requests are handled
This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changes to this privacy policy
The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by notifying its Users on this page and possibly within this Application and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habits Lab Terms of Service Agreement
By creating an account, you agree that your registration for and use of Habits Lab’s (“Habits Lab”, “we” or “our”) products and services is subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Habits Lab Terms of Service Agreement (this “Agreement”) and that this Agreement is enforceable like any written contract signed by you. If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, you shall not access, download, or otherwise use the Habits Lab Products and Services (as defined below). The Habits Lab Products and Services are licensed, not sold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Habits Lab provides a platform to track meals and questionnaire related information for individuals (collectively, the “Habits Lab Products and Services”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additional Policies
The following policies are incorporated into this Agreement by reference and provide additional terms and conditions related to specific Habits Lab Products and Services:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Habits Lab’s Website Privacy Policy: &lt;a href=&#34;https://habitslab.github.io/privacy&#34;&gt;https://habitslab.github.io/privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Habits Lab’s Website Terms of Use: &lt;a href=&#34;https://habitslab.github.io/terms&#34;&gt;https://habitslab.github.io/terms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each of these policies may be amended at any time and such amendments shall be binding and effective as indicated within such policies. In the event of any inconsistency between the Terms of Use and this Agreement, this Agreement shall govern your access to and use of the Habits Lab Products and Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;License
(a) Restrictions: You agree that you will access and use the Habits Lab Products and Services only in compliance with this Agreement. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree that you shall not, nor shall you permit others to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) allow anyone other than yourself to access the Habits Lab Products and Services, or any portion thereof, without Habits Lab’s express prior written permission;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(ii) use the Habits Lab Products and Services to create products or perform services which compete or interfere with the products and services of Habits Lab;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(iii) create compilations or derivative works of the Habits Lab Products and Services;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(iv) lend, sublicense, assign, sell or transfer the Habits Lab Products and Services, or any derivative works based thereon, in whole or in part, to any third party;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(v) copy any portion of the Habits Lab Products and Services in any fashion that may infringe any copyright, intellectual property right, contractual right, or proprietary or property right or interest held by Habits Lab or any other third party;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(vi) remove or obscure any copyright notice or other notice or terms of use contained in the Habits Lab Products and Services;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(vii) remove, disable, avoid, circumvent, or defeat any functionality in the Habits Lab Products and Services designed to limit or control access to or use of the Habits Lab Products and Services; or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(viii) use, download or otherwise access any portion of the Habits Lab Products and Services for which you have not made payment to Habits Lab. If for any reason, you access such Habits Lab Products and Services, these terms and conditions apply to your use of such services and you agree to pay all applicable charges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(e) No Enhancements: Certain Habits Lab Products and Services may be customized to fit your unique needs. Notwithstanding the foregoing or Section 3(b) above, this Agreement does not entitle you to any enhancements, customizations and modifications of the Habits Lab Products and Services, nor to ancillary products, unless agreed to by Habits Lab. Accordingly, you understand that we may modify or otherwise enhance the Habits Lab Products and Services at any time and in doing so incur no obligation to furnish such updates to you pursuant to this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(f) Limitations on Reverse Engineering, Decompilation, and Disassembly: You may not copy, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, derive source code, modify or prepare derivative works of the Habits Lab Products and Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(g) Non-exclusive License: This license is non-exclusive and nothing herein shall limit Habits Lab’s right to sell, assign, or in any other manner transfer Habits Lab’s ownership of any Habits Lab Products and Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Term and Renewals
This Agreement (and your subscription) is effective for an unlimited period of time from the beginning of your use of Habits Lab products and services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User Accounts
Use of User ID: Habits Lab relies on User IDs to know whether users accessing the Website and using the Habits Lab Products and Services are authorized to do so. You are solely responsible for any and all access to the Website or use of the Subscribed Services by persons using a User ID associated with your Profile. Please notify us immediately if you become aware that a User ID associated with your Profile is being used without authorization. Habits Lab will not be liable to you or to any third party for any use (whether authorized or unauthorized) of your account, Profile or associated User ID. You acknowledge and agree that Habits Lab may access and/or disclose your account, Profile and associated User ID and related information if required to do so by law or if Habits Lab has a reasonable belief that such actions are reasonably required to (i) respond to claims that any material made available by you though the Website infringes, misappropriates or violates any third-party rights, (ii) comply with legal obligations imposed on Habits Lab or any subpoenas, investigative demands, or court orders directed to Habits Lab, (iii) enforce or fulfill the obligations under this Agreement, or (iv) protect the rights, property or safety of Habits Lab and its users and the general public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warranties and Limitation of Liabilities
(a) No Warranty: THE SERVICES PROVIDED ON THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS”, AS-AVAILABLE BASIS. WE, OUR DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, ADVISORS AND AGENTS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY, BY USAGE OF TRADE, COURSE OF DEALING OR OTHERWISE WITH RESPECT TO THE CAPABILITY OF THE SERVICES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WITH RESPECT TO ACCESS TO THE SERVICES THROUGH ANY MOBILE DEVICE) OR THE ACCURACY OR THE COMPLETENESS OF THE DATA PROVIDED THEREIN. ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY TYPE, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WITH RESPECT TO WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE, SATISFACTORY QUALITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED. ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL ACCESSED, DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICES BY ANY MEANS WHATSOEVER IS AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM, LOSS OF DATA, FAILURE TO TRANSMIT DATA OR ANY OTHER LOSS THAT RESULTS FROM ACCESSING, DOWNLOADING, USING OR RELYING ON ANY SUCH MATERIAL. Habits Lab DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES PROVIDED HEREIN WILL MEET ANY PARTICULAR CRITERIA OF PERFORMANCE OR QUALITY, OR THAT THE WEBSITE IS FREE OF OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Limitations of Liability: NOTWITHSTANDING ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THIS AGREEMENT, Habits Lab’S LIABILITY UNDER THIS AGREEMENT, WHETHER UNDER CONTRACT LAW, TORT LAW OR OTHERWISE, SHALL BE LIMITED TO DIRECT DAMAGES NOT TO EXCEED THE OPTIONAL SUBSCRIPTION FEES PAID BY YOU TO Habits Lab IN THE THEN CURRENT YEAR OF THIS AGREEMENT, WHICH, FOR THE PURPOSES HEREOF, SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE SUBSCRIBED SERVICES WITHOUT MODIFICATION OR CUSTOMIZATION OR OTHER UPGRADES OR UPDATES THAT ARE PROVIDED BY Habits Lab TO YOU UNDER ANY OTHER AGREEMENT. WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, IN NO EVENT SHALL Habits Lab, ITS SUPPLIERS AND ITS AFFILIATES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHER DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, PRODUCT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE services OR THE FAILURE TO PROVIDE SUPPORT SERVICES, EVEN IF Habits Lab HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. Habits Lab EXPRESSLY DENIES ANY RESPONSIBILITY RESULTING FROM HACKING, TAMPERING, OR OTHER UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR USE OF THE SERVICES OR YOUR ACCOUNT OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREIN. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED OR HARMED BY Habits Lab OR ANYTHING RELATED TO Habits Lab (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE SUBSCRIBED SERVICES), YOU MAY CANCEL YOUR Habits Lab ACCOUNT AND TERMINATE THIS AGREEMENT IN ACCORDANCE WITH SECTION 5 (Fees and Payment) OR SECTION 10 (TERMINATION), AS APPLICABLE, AND SUCH TERMINATION SHALL BE YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY (AND Habits Lab’S SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE LIABILITY). THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(c) Indemnity: YOU SHALL INDEMNIFY AND HOLD Habits Lab AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, AGENTS, ADVISORS AND EMPLOYEES, HARMLESS FROM ALL CLAIMS, THREATS, ACTIONS, PROCEEDINGS, DEMANDS, DAMAGES, LOSSES, OBLIGATIONS, COSTS, AND EXPENSES INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS’ FEES, MADE BY ANY THIRD PARTY DUE TO OR ARISING OUT OF MATERIALS SUBMITTED, POSTED, TRANSMITTED OR MADE AVAILABLE BY YOU THROUGH THE WEBSITE, YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, ANY VIOLATION BY YOU OF THE TERMS OF USE OR THIS AGREEMENT, OR ANY VIOLATION BY YOU OF ANY RIGHTS OF ANOTHER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS AND RIGHTS OF PUBLICITY, PERSONALITY OR PRIVACY).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(d) Reliance on Limitations: You expressly acknowledge that Habits Lab is entering into this Agreement and is making the Website and Habits Lab Products and Services available to you in reliance upon the limitations and exclusions of liability and the disclaimers set forth herein and that the same form an essential basis of the contract between you and Habits Lab. You expressly agree that the limitations and exclusions of liability and the disclaimers set forth herein will survive, and continue to apply in the case of, termination of this Agreement for any reason, a fundamental breach or breaches of this Agreement, the failure of essential purpose of this Agreement, the failure of any exclusive remedy or the termination or suspension by Habits Lab of your use of, or access to, the Website or the Habits Lab Products and Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;7&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proprietary Rights
(a) Trade Secrets and Confidential Information: You acknowledge and agree that any and all confidential information and materials from which Habits Lab derives actual or potential economic value constitutes Habits Lab’s confidential and proprietary trade secrets (collectively, “Trade Secrets”). You further acknowledge and agree that Habits Lab’s Trade Secrets include, but are not limited to, the Habits Lab Products and Services, and the technology used therein. Except as permitted under this Agreement, you shall maintain any information learned about Habits Lab’s Trade Secrets as confidential and shall not disclose such information or permit such information to be disclosed to any person or entity. With respect to all such information, you shall exercise the same degree of care to protect Habits Lab’s Trade Secrets that you exercise with respect to protecting your own confidential information, and in no event less than reasonable care.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Ownership in the Habits Lab Products and Services: All right, title and interest and all intellectual property rights in and to the Habits Lab Products and Services (including but not limited to the source code, object code, diagrams, specifications, and any images, photographs, animations, video, audio, music, text, and ‘applets’ incorporated therein), are owned by Habits Lab. We are not granting any license to you under any intellectual property rights by virtue of this Agreement, except for the limited right to use the Website and your unlimited Trial Period and Subscribed Services in accordance with this Agreement. Other product and company names that are mentioned on the Website or provided under this Agreement may be trademarks of their respective owners. We reserve all rights that are not expressly granted to you in this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(c) Proprietary Notices: You will not remove any Habits Lab patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary notices from any part of the Website or Habits Lab Products and Services and shall reproduce such notices in any copies, in whole or in part, of such materials permitted to be made by you hereunder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(d) Upgrades and Customization: Any enhancement, upgrade or modification of the Habits Lab Products and Services, if any, and any customization undertaken by Habits Lab on your behalf shall be the sole and complete property of Habits Lab and you shall have no ownership right or claim thereto under any circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(e) Trademarks: This Agreement does not grant you any rights in connection with any of Habits Lab’s trademarks or trade names in any way, including in any promotion or publication, without Habits Lab’s prior written consent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(f) Injunctive Relief: You acknowledge that the breach of any of your obligations under this Section 7 will, or is likely to, cause irreparable harm, and accordingly, Habits Lab will be entitled to seek equitable relief to protect its interests therein, including preliminary and permanent injunctive relief, as well as monetary damages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amendments to this Agreement
Habits Lab may amend this Agreement at any time. Any such amendment shall be binding and effective upon the earlier of (i) the date that is thirty (30) days after posting of the amended Agreement on the Website, or (ii) the date that Habits Lab provides notice to you of the amended Agreement pursuant to the notice provisions in this Agreement; except that changes to fees and payment terms shall only be effective in respect of payments made after such changes are posted or notified. You may immediately terminate this Agreement upon notice to Habits Lab if a change is unacceptable to you. Your continued use of your optional subscription following any amendment to this Agreement shall constitute your acceptance of the amendment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Non-Transferable
You shall not assign this Agreement or your subscription without the express written consent of Habits Lab. Any attempted assignment in violation of this provision shall be null and void.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;General
(a) Governing Law: This Agreement shall be construed in accordance with, and all disputes hereunder shall be governed by, the laws of the United States therein, excluding its conflicts of law rules. Any suit or claim hereunder will be brought solely in the courts located in Chicago, Illinois having jurisdiction therefor. The parties specifically disclaim the applicability of the United Nations convention on contracts for the international sale of goods to this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Severability: If a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of this Agreement invalid or unenforceable, that provision of this Agreement will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible and the other provisions of this Agreement will remain in full force and effect; provided that severance of any payment term with the result that Habits Lab will not be compensated at the rates and on the terms provided for herein, shall result in immediate termination of this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(c) No Waiver: The failure by either party to enforce any provision of this Agreement will not constitute a waiver of future enforcement of that or any other provision and such waiver will only be valid and in enforceable if made by the waiving party in writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If to you:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through your Habits Lab account or to the address noted in the registration information completed by you, as such may be updated from time to time in accordance with this Agreement. You acknowledge and agree that Habits Lab shall have no liability associated with or arising from your failure to maintain accurate contact or other information with us, including, but not limited to, your failure to receive critical information about the optional Subscribed Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If to Habits Lab:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:habitslab@northwestern.edu&#34;&gt;habitslab@northwestern.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any notice shall be deemed delivered on the third business day after the date mailed or on the business day of delivery of electronic mail (or the next business day, if the electronic mail is sent by a party on a day that is not a business day or after 5:00pm local time in the jurisdiction of the transmitting party on a day that is a business day) in the manner set out above. The designation or address of the party to be notified may be changed at any time by delivery of notice of that change to the other party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(d) Force Majeure: Neither party will be responsible for any failure or delay in its performance under this Agreement (except for any payment obligations) due to causes beyond its reasonable control and not due to its fault or negligence, including, but not limited to, labour disputes, strikes, lockouts, shortages of or inability to obtain labour, or war, terrorism, riots, acts of God or any governmental action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(e) Independent Contractors: The parties to this Agreement are independent contractors and this Agreement will not establish any relationship of partnership, joint venture, employment, franchise, or agency between the parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(f) Entire Agreement: This Agreement and the policies, schedules, terms and conditions incorporated herein, including the Terms of Use, the Privacy Policy and the Fee Schedule constitute the entire, final and complete agreement between the parties and supersede all previous agreements, representations, oral or written relating to this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syncwise</title>
      <link>/project/syncwise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/syncwise/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SyncWISE: Window Induced Shift Estimation for Synchronization ofVideo and Accelerometry from Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/syncwisewindowinducedshiftestimationforsynchronizationofvideoandaccelerometryfromwearablesensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/syncwisewindowinducedshiftestimationforsynchronizationofvideoandaccelerometryfromwearablesensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NeckSense: A Multi-Sensor Necklace for Detecting Eating Activities in Free-Living Conditions</title>
      <link>/publication/necksenseamultisensornecklacefordetectingeatingactivitiesinfreelivingconditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/necksenseamultisensornecklacefordetectingeatingactivitiesinfreelivingconditions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is More Always Better?: Discovering Incentivized mHealth Intervention Engagement Related to Health Behavior Trends</title>
      <link>/publication/ismorealwaysbetterdiscoveringincentivizedmhealthinterventionengagementrelatedtohealthbehaviortrends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/ismorealwaysbetterdiscoveringincentivizedmhealthinterventionengagementrelatedtohealthbehaviortrends/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>micro-Stress EMA: A Passive Sensing Framework for Detecting in-the-wild Stress in Pregnant Mothers</title>
      <link>/publication/microstressemaapassivesensingframeworkfordetectinginthewildstressinpregnantmothers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/microstressemaapassivesensingframeworkfordetectinginthewildstressinpregnantmothers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Mask or Not to Mask? Balancing Privacy with Visual Confirmation Utility in Activity-Oriented Wearable Cameras</title>
      <link>/publication/tomaskornottomaskbalancingprivacywithvisualconfirmationutilityinactivityorientedwearablecameras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/tomaskornottomaskbalancingprivacywithvisualconfirmationutilityinactivityorientedwearablecameras/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can’t Be Myself: Effects ofWearable Cameras on the Capture of Authentic Behavior in the Wild</title>
      <link>/publication/icanatbemyselfeffectsofwearablecamerasonthecaptureofauthenticbehaviorinthewild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/icanatbemyselfeffectsofwearablecamerasonthecaptureofauthenticbehaviorinthewild/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Caloric Intake in Bedridden Hospital Patients with Audio and Neck-worn Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/estimatingcaloricintakeinbedriddenhospitalpatientswithaudioandneckwornsensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/estimatingcaloricintakeinbedriddenhospitalpatientswithaudioandneckwornsensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WillSense: Will Participants Wear Passive Sensing Devices Long Enough To Study Eating Behavior?</title>
      <link>/publication/willsensewillparticipantswearpassivesensingdeviceslongenoughtostudyeatingbehavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/willsensewillparticipantswearpassivesensingdeviceslongenoughtostudyeatingbehavior/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing Nigerian Food Items and Calorie Content with Hyperspectral Imaging</title>
      <link>/publication/distinguishingnigerianfooditemsandcaloriecontentwithhyperspectralimaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/distinguishingnigerianfooditemsandcaloriecontentwithhyperspectralimaging/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Generalized Eating Detection Machine Learning Models Fail in the Field</title>
      <link>/publication/whengeneralizedeatingdetectionmachinelearningmodelsfailinthefield/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/whengeneralizedeatingdetectionmachinelearningmodelsfailinthefield/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Sense Overeating: Motif-based Machine Learning Framework to Detect Overeating Using Wrist-worn Sensing</title>
      <link>/publication/isenseovereatingmotifbasedmachinelearningframeworktodetectovereatingusingwristwornsensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/isenseovereatingmotifbasedmachinelearningframeworktodetectovereatingusingwristwornsensing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WillSense: Adherence Barriers for Passive Sensing Systems that Track Eating Behavior</title>
      <link>/publication/willsenseadherencebarriersforpassivesensingsystemsthattrackeatingbehavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/willsenseadherencebarriersforpassivesensingsystemsthattrackeatingbehavior/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into the Brave New Transdiscipline of Mobile Health</title>
      <link>/publication/firststepsintothebravenewtransdisciplineofmobilehealth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/firststepsintothebravenewtransdisciplineofmobilehealth/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Barriers and Facilitators to Wearable Adherence in Fine-Grained Eating Detection</title>
      <link>/publication/investigatingbarriersandfacilitatorstowearableadherenceinfinegrainedeatingdetection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/investigatingbarriersandfacilitatorstowearableadherenceinfinegrainedeatingdetection/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwallowNet: Recurrent Neural Network Detects and Characterizes Eating Patterns</title>
      <link>/publication/swallownetrecurrentneuralnetworkdetectsandcharacterizeseatingpatterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/swallownetrecurrentneuralnetworkdetectsandcharacterizeseatingpatterns/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UStress: Understanding College Student Subjective Stress Using Wrist-Based Passive Sensing</title>
      <link>/publication/ustressunderstandingcollegestudentsubjectivestressusingwristbasedpassivesensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/ustressunderstandingcollegestudentsubjectivestressusingwristbasedpassivesensing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Watch: Detecting and Characterizing Eating Episodes through Feeding Gestures</title>
      <link>/publication/foodwatchdetectingandcharacterizingeatingepisodesthroughfeedinggestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/foodwatchdetectingandcharacterizingeatingepisodesthroughfeedinggestures/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartNecklace: Designing a Wearable Multi-sensor System for Smart Eating Detection</title>
      <link>/publication/smartnecklacedesigningawearablemultisensorsystemforsmarteatingdetection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/smartnecklacedesigningawearablemultisensorsystemforsmarteatingdetection/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Mixed-Effects Location Scale Model to Examine Factors That Influence Overeating Behaviors Among College Students</title>
      <link>/publication/usingamixedeffectslocationscalemodeltoexaminefactorsthatinfluenceovereatingbehaviorsamongcollegestudents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/usingamixedeffectslocationscalemodeltoexaminefactorsthatinfluenceovereatingbehaviorsamongcollegestudents/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Conceptual Models of Engagement in an mHealth Intervention Application</title>
      <link>/publication/improvedconceptualmodelsofengagementinanmhealthinterventionapplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/improvedconceptualmodelsofengagementinanmhealthinterventionapplication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Algorithms Applied to Detect Feeding Gestures</title>
      <link>/publication/machinelearningalgorithmsappliedtodetectfeedinggestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/machinelearningalgorithmsappliedtodetectfeedinggestures/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Forests Detects Eating in a Neck-worn Sensor: Results from a Simulated Real-Life Eating Setting</title>
      <link>/publication/randomforestsdetectseatinginaneckwornsensorresultsfromasimulatedreallifeeatingsetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/randomforestsdetectseatinginaneckwornsensorresultsfromasimulatedreallifeeatingsetting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Iterative Dimensionality-Scaling System for Real-Time Health Monitoring Applications</title>
      <link>/publication/aniterativedimensionalityscalingsystemforrealtimehealthmonitoringapplications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/aniterativedimensionalityscalingsystemforrealtimehealthmonitoringapplications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internal Project</title>
      <link>/project/internal-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/internal-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Duis posuere tellus ac convallis placerat. Proin tincidunt magna sed ex sollicitudin condimentum. Sed ac faucibus dolor, scelerisque sollicitudin nisi. Cras purus urna, suscipit quis sapien eu, pulvinar tempor diam. Quisque risus orci, mollis id ante sit amet, gravida egestas nisl. Sed ac tempus magna. Proin in dui enim. Donec condimentum, sem id dapibus fringilla, tellus enim condimentum arcu, nec volutpat est felis vel metus. Vestibulum sit amet erat at nulla eleifend gravida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nullam vel molestie justo. Curabitur vitae efficitur leo. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Sed pulvinar mauris dui, eget varius purus congue ac. Nulla euismod, lorem vel elementum dapibus, nunc justo porta mi, sed tempus est est vel tellus. Nam et enim eleifend, laoreet sem sit amet, elementum sem. Morbi ut leo congue, maximus velit ut, finibus arcu. In et libero cursus, rutrum risus non, molestie leo. Nullam congue quam et volutpat malesuada. Sed risus tortor, pulvinar et dictum nec, sodales non mi. Phasellus lacinia commodo laoreet. Nam mollis, erat in feugiat consectetur, purus eros egestas tellus, in auctor urna odio at nibh. Mauris imperdiet nisi ac magna convallis, at rhoncus ligula cursus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cras aliquam rhoncus ipsum, in hendrerit nunc mattis vitae. Duis vitae efficitur metus, ac tempus leo. Cras nec fringilla lacus. Quisque sit amet risus at ipsum pharetra commodo. Sed aliquam mauris at consequat eleifend. Praesent porta, augue sed viverra bibendum, neque ante euismod ante, in vehicula justo lorem ac eros. Suspendisse augue libero, venenatis eget tincidunt ut, malesuada at lorem. Donec vitae bibendum arcu. Aenean maximus nulla non pretium iaculis. Quisque imperdiet, nulla in pulvinar aliquet, velit quam ultrices quam, sit amet fringilla leo sem vel nunc. Mauris in lacinia lacus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspendisse a tincidunt lacus. Curabitur at urna sagittis, dictum ante sit amet, euismod magna. Sed rutrum massa id tortor commodo, vitae elementum turpis tempus. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean purus turpis, venenatis a ullamcorper nec, tincidunt et massa. Integer posuere quam rutrum arcu vehicula imperdiet. Mauris ullamcorper quam vitae purus congue, quis euismod magna eleifend. Vestibulum semper vel augue eget tincidunt. Fusce eget justo sodales, dapibus odio eu, ultrices lorem. Duis condimentum lorem id eros commodo, in facilisis mauris scelerisque. Morbi sed auctor leo. Nullam volutpat a lacus quis pharetra. Nulla congue rutrum magna a ornare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquam in turpis accumsan, malesuada nibh ut, hendrerit justo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Quisque sed erat nec justo posuere suscipit. Donec ut efficitur arcu, in malesuada neque. Nunc dignissim nisl massa, id vulputate nunc pretium nec. Quisque eget urna in risus suscipit ultricies. Pellentesque odio odio, tincidunt in eleifend sed, posuere a diam. Nam gravida nisl convallis semper elementum. Morbi vitae felis faucibus, vulputate orci placerat, aliquet nisi. Aliquam erat volutpat. Maecenas sagittis pulvinar purus, sed porta quam laoreet at.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Wearable Sensor System for Medication Adherence Prediction</title>
      <link>/publication/awearablesensorsystemformedicationadherenceprediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/awearablesensorsystemformedicationadherenceprediction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Piezoelectric-based Inertial Sensing and Audio-based Detection of Swallows</title>
      <link>/publication/acomparisonofpiezoelectricbasedinertialsensingandaudiobaseddetectionofswallows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/acomparisonofpiezoelectricbasedinertialsensingandaudiobaseddetectionofswallows/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Electronic Methods for Non-Invasive Detection of Eating Behavior</title>
      <link>/publication/asurveyofelectronicmethodsfornoninvasivedetectionofeatingbehavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/asurveyofelectronicmethodsfornoninvasivedetectionofeatingbehavior/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Computation Offloading for Low-Power Wearable Health Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/dynamiccomputationoffloadingforlowpowerwearablehealthmonitoringsystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/dynamiccomputationoffloadingforlowpowerwearablehealthmonitoringsystems/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Segmentation of Time-Series Audio Signals using Support Vector Machines</title>
      <link>/publication/probabilisticsegmentationoftimeseriesaudiosignalsusingsupportvectormachines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/probabilisticsegmentationoftimeseriesaudiosignalsusingsupportvectormachines/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Health Monitoring Outcome Success Prediction using First Month Intervention Data</title>
      <link>/publication/remotehealthmonitoringoutcomesuccesspredictionusingfirstmonthinterventiondata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/remotehealthmonitoringoutcomesuccesspredictionusingfirstmonthinterventiondata/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detection of Gestures Associated with Medication Adherence using Smartwatch-based Inertial Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/detectionofgesturesassociatedwithmedicationadherenceusingsmartwatchbasedinertialsensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/detectionofgesturesassociatedwithmedicationadherenceusingsmartwatchbasedinertialsensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Based Detection and Evaluation of Eating Behavior using the Smartwatch Platform</title>
      <link>/publication/audiobaseddetectionandevaluationofeatingbehaviorusingthesmartwatchplatform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/audiobaseddetectionandevaluationofeatingbehaviorusingthesmartwatchplatform/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Coaching on Adherence in Remote Health Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/effectsofcoachingonadherenceinremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/effectsofcoachingonadherenceinremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Feature Extraction Framework for Predicting the Severity of Condition for Congestive Heart Failure Patients</title>
      <link>/publication/adatadrivenfeatureextractionframeworkforpredictingtheseverityofconditionforcongestiveheartfailurepatients/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/adatadrivenfeatureextractionframeworkforpredictingtheseverityofconditionforcongestiveheartfailurepatients/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Smartwatch-Based Medication Adherence System</title>
      <link>/publication/asmartwatchbasedmedicationadherencesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/asmartwatchbasedmedicationadherencesystem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Eating Habits using a Piezoelectric Sensor-Based Necklace</title>
      <link>/publication/monitoringeatinghabitsusingapiezoelectricsensorbasednecklace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/monitoringeatinghabitsusingapiezoelectricsensorbasednecklace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Invasive Detection of Medication Adherence using a Digital Smart Necklace</title>
      <link>/publication/noninvasivedetectionofmedicationadherenceusingadigitalsmartnecklace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/noninvasivedetectionofmedicationadherenceusingadigitalsmartnecklace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Optimization for Wearable Devices</title>
      <link>/publication/poweroptimizationforwearabledevices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/poweroptimizationforwearabledevices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recognition of Nutrition-Intake using Time-Frequency Decomposition in a Wearable Necklace using a Piezoelectric Sensor</title>
      <link>/publication/recognitionofnutritionintakeusingtimefrequencydecompositioninawearablenecklaceusingapiezoelectricsensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/recognitionofnutritionintakeusingtimefrequencydecompositioninawearablenecklaceusingapiezoelectricsensor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Predicting Adherence in Remote Health Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/aframeworkforpredictingadherenceinremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/aframeworkforpredictingadherenceinremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Dr. Google: Early Results of a Personalized Weight-Tracking Smartphone Application and Alert System for Patients with Ascites</title>
      <link>/publication/beyonddrgoogleearlyresultsofapersonalizedweighttrackingsmartphoneapplicationandalertsystemforpatientswithascites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/beyonddrgoogleearlyresultsofapersonalizedweighttrackingsmartphoneapplicationandalertsystemforpatientswithascites/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Model Analytics for Adverse Event Prediction in Remote Health Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/multiplemodelanalyticsforadverseeventpredictioninremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/multiplemodelanalyticsforadverseeventpredictioninremotehealthmonitoringsystems/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Invasive Monitoring of Eating Behavior using Spectrogram Analysis in a Wearable Necklace</title>
      <link>/publication/noninvasivemonitoringofeatingbehaviorusingspectrogramanalysisinawearablenecklace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/noninvasivemonitoringofeatingbehaviorusingspectrogramanalysisinawearablenecklace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectrogram-Based Audio Classification of Nutrition Intake</title>
      <link>/publication/spectrogrambasedaudioclassificationofnutritionintake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/spectrogrambasedaudioclassificationofnutritionintake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Vector Regression for METs of Exergaming Actions</title>
      <link>/publication/supportvectorregressionformetsofexergamingactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/supportvectorregressionformetsofexergamingactions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Electronic Health Records to Predict Severity of Condition for Congestive Heart Failure Patients</title>
      <link>/publication/usingelectronichealthrecordstopredictseverityofconditionforcongestiveheartfailurepatients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/usingelectronichealthrecordstopredictseverityofconditionforcongestiveheartfailurepatients/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Health Monitoring: Predicting Outcome Success based on Contextual Features for Cardiovascular Disease</title>
      <link>/publication/remotehealthmonitoringpredictingoutcomesuccessbasedoncontextualfeaturesforcardiovasculardisease/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/remotehealthmonitoringpredictingoutcomesuccessbasedoncontextualfeaturesforcardiovasculardisease/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BreathSens: A Continuous On-Bed Respiratory Monitoring System With Torso Localization Using an Unobtrusive Pressure Sensing Array</title>
      <link>/publication/breathsensacontinuousonbedrespiratorymonitoringsystemwithtorsolocalizationusinganunobtrusivepressuresensingarray/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/breathsensacontinuousonbedrespiratorymonitoringsystemwithtorsolocalizationusinganunobtrusivepressuresensingarray/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Wearable Nutrition Monitoring System</title>
      <link>/publication/awearablenutritionmonitoringsystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/awearablenutritionmonitoringsystem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Cheating: Detecting Self-Inflicted and Impersonator Cheaters for Remote Health Monitoring Systems with Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/anticheatingdetectingselfinflictedandimpersonatorcheatersforremotehealthmonitoringsystemswithwearablesensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/anticheatingdetectingselfinflictedandimpersonatorcheatersforremotehealthmonitoringsystemswithwearablesensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determining the Single Best Axis for Exercise Repetition Recognition and Counting on SmartWatches</title>
      <link>/publication/determiningthesinglebestaxisforexerciserepetitionrecognitionandcountingonsmartwatches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/determiningthesinglebestaxisforexerciserepetitionrecognitionandcountingonsmartwatches/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving Compliance in Remote Healthcare Systems Through Smartphone Battery Optimization</title>
      <link>/publication/improvingcomplianceinremotehealthcaresystemsthroughsmartphonebatteryoptimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/improvingcomplianceinremotehealthcaresystemsthroughsmartphonebatteryoptimization/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battery Optimization in Smartphones for Remote Health Monitoring Systems to Enhance User Adherence</title>
      <link>/publication/batteryoptimizationinsmartphonesforremotehealthmonitoringsystemstoenhanceuseradherence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/batteryoptimizationinsmartphonesforremotehealthmonitoringsystemstoenhanceuseradherence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-invasive nutrition monitor</title>
      <link>/publication/noninvasivenutritionmonitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/noninvasivenutritionmonitor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying Connected: a CVD Risk Intervention for Young Black Women</title>
      <link>/publication/stayingconnectedacvdriskinterventionforyoungblackwomen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/stayingconnectedacvdriskinterventionforyoungblackwomen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Pressure Map Sequences for Recognition of On Bed Rehabilitation Exercises</title>
      <link>/publication/usingpressuremapsequencesforrecognitionofonbedrehabilitationexercises/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/usingpressuremapsequencesforrecognitionofonbedrehabilitationexercises/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Patient Monitoring: What Impact Can Data Analytics Have on Cost?</title>
      <link>/publication/remotepatientmonitoringwhatimpactcandataanalyticshaveoncost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/remotepatientmonitoringwhatimpactcandataanalyticshaveoncost/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Robust Activity Recognition Framework for Health and Exergaming Using Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/designingarobustactivityrecognitionframeworkforhealthandexergamingusingwearablesensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/designingarobustactivityrecognitionframeworkforhealthandexergamingusingwearablesensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Posture Analysis Using a Dense Pressure Sensitive Bedsheet</title>
      <link>/publication/sleeppostureanalysisusingadensepressuresensitivebedsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/sleeppostureanalysisusingadensepressuresensitivebedsheet/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving Accuracy in E-textiles as a Platform for Pervasive Sensing</title>
      <link>/publication/improvingaccuracyinetextilesasaplatformforpervasivesensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/improvingaccuracyinetextilesasaplatformforpervasivesensing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inconspicuous On-bed Respiratory Rate Monitoring</title>
      <link>/publication/inconspicuousonbedrespiratoryratemonitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/inconspicuousonbedrespiratoryratemonitoring/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MET Calculations From on-body Accelerometers for Exergaming Movements</title>
      <link>/publication/metcalculationsfromonbodyaccelerometersforexergamingmovements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/metcalculationsfromonbodyaccelerometersforexergamingmovements/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On-bed Monitoring for Range of Motion Exercises With a Pressure Sensitive Bedsheet</title>
      <link>/publication/onbedmonitoringforrangeofmotionexerciseswithapressuresensitivebedsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/onbedmonitoringforrangeofmotionexerciseswithapressuresensitivebedsheet/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust Human Intensity-varying Activity Recognition Using Stochastic Approximation in Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>/publication/robusthumanintensityvaryingactivityrecognitionusingstochasticapproximationinwearablesensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/robusthumanintensityvaryingactivityrecognitionusingstochasticapproximationinwearablesensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dense Pressure Sensitive Bedsheet Design for Unobtrusive Sleep Posture Monitoring</title>
      <link>/publication/adensepressuresensitivebedsheetdesignforunobtrusivesleepposturemonitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/adensepressuresensitivebedsheetdesignforunobtrusivesleepposturemonitoring/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Task Optimization in Remote Diabetes Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/dynamic_task_optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/dynamic_task_optimization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


Supplementary notes can be added here, including [code and math](https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/). --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opportunistic Hierarchical Classification for Power Optimization in Wearable Movement Monitoring Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/opportunistic-hierarchical-classification-for-power-optimization-in-wearable-movement-monitoring-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/opportunistic-hierarchical-classification-for-power-optimization-in-wearable-movement-monitoring-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


Supplementary notes can be added here, including [code and math](https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/). --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WANDA: an End-to-end Remote Health Monitoring and Analytics System for Heart Failure Patients</title>
      <link>/publication/wandaanendtoendremotehealthmonitoringandanalyticssystemforheartfailurepatients/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/wandaanendtoendremotehealthmonitoringandanalyticssystemforheartfailurepatients/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


Supplementary notes can be added here, including [code and math](https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/). --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Spider: Eight-legged Arachnid and Autonomous Learning of Locomotion</title>
      <link>/publication/artificial-spider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/artificial-spider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo Academic&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


Supplementary notes can be added here, including [code and math](https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/). --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
